Twenty twenty five, one of the invitations, but that's the first step to chair.
Chair Kindle.
I'll thank you for the day and thank you for this council.
Thank you for your protection, our officers and our town.
This last week in, and Father, I just pray that you continue to bless our town.
Give wisdom to this council, our leaders, and Father, we want to see your hand.
All this town, we want to see your life shine bright.
And you should bless my Emma in a special way.
Just be with us meeting tonight.
Thank you for these are here.
Thank you for that.
Amen.
I'd like to read just to the fire.
I'll keep you by the site of America.
And to the recovery for resistance.
Foundation.
I'm a god.
And it is a little regrettable.
And just for all.
A bore.
But again, bless me.
Let's go to the personal presence.
Bye.
Plain bliss.
Motion to approve.
Second.
A step back.
Don't go.
Jim.
Barnes.
I.
Six.
Tetra Tech claim for principal at G.R.D.A.
relaxing thing in civil litigation amount of 17,486 dollars in 50.
Yes, board.
Good evening.
This is for.
Tetra Tech claim for 17,486 dollars in 50 cents.
If this is approved tonight.
It will leave it remaining balance of 240,000.
If all five invoices related to the G.R.D.
claims presented are approved tonight.
We'll be at 137.
917.
Indeed, WT is very well aware.
They've tried to make enough like our remaining budget.
And you know, when you need to stick to that budget.
If all possible and everything.
So.
I know Shannon's work very hard to keep.
They're crossing down so we can finish the year.
On budget.
Second.
Jim.
Hi.
E.S.
Barnes.
I don't go.
Hi.
Parker.
Seven.
Really.
Good morning.
I'm going.
I'm just about a 60 million 100.
My.
Do you see it? I've pulled it up on the website. We can't get in your own. Sorry. Sorry about that. Yeah, yeah
Do you want to look at this blessed?
Smaller on pay of works. As I said, that's how tight our budget is. We're sharing it. I think I'll make a motion. We approve
Hey, I'll provide the trust manager and city of Toronto to go shade and execute a contract
with uptown services for the design of a vibrant network. Yeah, so this is the exciting agenda item for tonight
This would be for us to hire uptown services to design like blessed our fiber system for the community
You know, since I've been here we've had a lot of people that say they want to come in bring fiber, you know, you already
All of it, but I mean, nobody's yet to come in. I'm sure as we start to design somebody else will come out of the work
So they want to come in. I just think you know besides the revenues, there's also a lot of intrinsic values
As you know, the police you can talk about putting cameras around the community that we get picked up, you know, the last players on, you know, I think of like the softball fields and the baseball fields thus having internet there and then Kevin could sell ads or like why if I use his or something, you know, I mean there's lots of good things to do.
So, I've found services to the company that did our ROI study, you know, a few years ago.
I'm going to show that, you know, it's a very good project. He said they've done 70-some as of today.
He put ours in the top 10 percent as far as, you know, success.
This, I reached out to some of their companies that they've done work for.
They did work for sales, so they did design sales, but they helped them keep everything going right now.
And sales also, they would hire them to get in a heartbeat.
I talked to a gentleman named Michael Gardner at the City of Glenwood Springs.
He said we definitely would, this is actually a ZML.
We had them do a feasibility study design and some implementation work happened to kick off the project off in 2020.
And their help was invaluable in planning and implemented implementation process.
Then I got reached out to Monroe Johnson, the chief technology officer for a co-op, you know, electric co-op.
He said I would definitely use up-down services again that have been our engineering firm from the beginning of our fiber-to-the-home project.
And I've worked with them for over 11 years. They're knowledgeable and responsive, and I would highly recommend them with the exclamation marks.
So, just asking the board for approval tonight to me for, I guess if I had my way, we would approve it.
And then three, four, five months, we would have a big ribbon cutting with our first fiber strand ran or something like that all the board there.
What's the matter there?
Is the question too awkward?
Potion to approve?
I guess.
So cool.
Five.
Thank you.
Nine.
Other new business.
If any, which is in prison since the posting of this agenda,
Jim Jones, he can get announcements.
I'll have an agreement.
Motion.
Second.
Five.
Four.